Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION.
Look at the trouble we're going through
to make that foul creature live.
Cruel world.
I forged the steel thoroughly, Batur Bey.
No one in this world can defeat you now.
If it lets me down during a battle...
... then no one can save you from
me, blacksmith.
I wonder what you're up to now.
All of them were lies.
Kalonoz.
- Listen to me.
- God damn you.
Stop!
Who are you?
We are the only force that will get
Byzantine back on its feet.
Commander Kalonoz.
We're the only masters of that
great, holy power.
We swore to fight the Turks and bring our
empire to its former glory...
... and protect Hagia Sophia in
Constantinople.
Who are you?
Yannis. Monk Yannis.
I'm a loyal servant of the Margaret
Church in Serres.
Everyone you see here, in the name of
our church, are guards of Kulucahisar.
Kulucahisar is just one of the castles
under our control.
Many more castles, with their commanders,
soldiers, and even governors...
... are under our control.
Sofia.
What about you?
Growing with the hate of the Turkish...
... I'm a woman who has always
obeyed Master Yannis.
I'm a woman who couldn't tell her
feelings...
... to the man she loved, because
of this cause.
I offer a commander like you to
join us....
... to become more powerful, and to
fight the Turks until the end...
... Commander Kalonoz.
Tell me.
What were you looking for in the castle?
It's obvious that you took
something hidden.
Was it, the treasure?
You're right, Osman. It was the treasure.
But we neither stole nor seized it.
With the help and grace of Allah, we
took back what was ours.
That treasure in its entirety, belongs
to the Ahis.
I know Ahis, and how they
withstand to Mongolians.
But I'm uncomfortable, Edebali.
Why are the ones in the castle opposed
you? Why did they steal your treasure?
What happened in the castle?
Your daughter Bala, Father Tursun, why
were they there?
A dark force ruling Bithynia has spread
everywhere, every corner.
Sometimes they dominate with their
ideas...
... and sometimes with the men they pick.
What do they want? What are they after?
They want to end our beliefs with
the darkness they laid upon us, son.
They want to kick the Turks out of
these lands and revive Byzantine's spirit.
They know Ahis won't surrender.
To be ahead of us, they stole the
treasure that is Ahis' fortune.
They want to push us into an
economic crisis, son.
Even Sofia who killed the governor and
captured the castle...
... is their agent in the castle.
The ones who stole this treasure from
you, as you described...
... a dark and great power, Edebali.
The force behind the ones who believe in
Allah, is always greater, son.
We neither have concerns, nor fears.
We know and believe that no matter how
angry the enemy's armies are...
... there is a Mount Hira for every
truth.
The things you've told me cheered me up.
I have a strong feeling that, during
all this trouble...
... what we need is a strong union.
A majestic union no enemy can weaken.
Maybe...
... maybe even a state.
This shall be such a state that with
it, justice should be revived.
Islamic world shall find peace.
The cruel shall shake, manners shall rise
up with it.
Don't be surprised, Commander Kalonoz.
Just answer.
Are you with us?
Let's say I'm not.
Will kill me too?
No commander who has no hatred for the
Turkish, has the right to live, Kalonoz.
We set off for a great cause.
And our enemies are so close that...
... there is absolutely no room in
our hearts for mercy.
Who are those enemies?
Sheikh Edebali, and his Ahis.
An old Sheikh, and a handful of Ahis.
Why do they bother you so
much, Monk Yannis?
You don't know them, Kalonoz.
Sheikh Edebali is the soul of the Turkish
who cannot be captured.
Even the Mongolians
couldn't deal with Ahis.
The moment we think they are done
with, they will start a new beginning.
Then, how will you deal with them?
With heroes like you, who kill and die
for their causes.
We Greeks, have an ancient saying.
If you're going to hunt wolfs, sharpen
your axe.
If we don't sharpen our axes, we can't
oppose the Turkish.
And if we can't oppose them, Sheikh
Edebali and his Ahis...
... will unite with Ghazis (Veterans),
Alps (Men), Bacıyans (Women)...
... and that will be our doom.
Now I will ask again, Commander Kalonoz.
After many years, do you want to be
remembered as a traitor...
... or as a hero who stopped the
Turks' rush?
In this holy journey,
I'm with you until my death.
Shut your mouth. Shut up!
Shut up!
Only if my Osman Bey didn't need you...
... so I could skin you alive.
I told you everything I knew. Let me go!
Shut up. Shut up!
Open it, open it!
Now sit here quietly.
One question, one answer.
Who are you?
- Peace be with you.
- Friends.
Peace be with you too.
Separate the double and single-threaded
ones well.
The ones with patterns are still
incomplete.
We can't sell them like this in the
bazaar.
- Very well, Bala Hatun.
These ones are not suitable for selling.
Turn them into boots for the unfortunate
and give them away.
Very well, Bala Hatun.
Not only in swinging swords, but you're
also skilled in trading, Bala Hatun.
We can protect our lives with swords,
Turks' dignity with trade...
... and traditions with our manners,
Osman Bey.
The Turkish's traditions are on women's
hands, my dear mother used to say.
Thanks to you, I realised how right
she was.
Bala Hatun.
- Your horse Alaca.
- What happened to Alaca?
The situation is not good in the barn.
No grass can grow in your path, my friend.
Bala Hatun's wing, my Alaca.
I'd never known I'd see you like this.
He jumped right out of the Epic of Manas
to my life, Osman Bey.
He was my guide.
Like the moon in the sky, My Alaca was my
crescent with its light in the dark.
My Alaca.
Excuse him, Bala Hatun.
How can you be mad at the moon
because of dark clouds?
You've gone through such things with
Bala Hatun, gone through such battles...
It can be seen from your scars.
You are brave just like your owner.
You don't give up, you don't surrender.
It's obvious that you do your
horse good, Bala Hatun.
You love him like a friend, ride him
like a foe.
And he endured in silence...
... didn't say anything despite the
infection in his stomach.
For you.
If you have faith in me...
... allow me to heal Alaca, like you
saved me from the mud.
I have faith in you, so I introduced you
to my father, Osman Bey.
Take care of my horse.
Alaca. Alaca.
It'll take care of the infection in
your stomach.
Now...
... I say we take you to the Tent.
I'll treat you there. So...
... not another tear falls from your
owner Bala Hatun's beautiful eyes.
May Allah bless you, Osman Bey.
My only wish...
... is you allow me to see you again
in the bazaar tomorrow.
My companion is in your hands.
I allow it, Osman Bey.
No matter what, I'll bring Alaca back.
In the 99 names of Allah, who calls into
being, fills our hearts with faith.
Everyone is awaiting orders to get their
swords, and punish them.
But, Dündar Bey, it seems like
you're stalling us.
I understand your pain and
anger, Bamsı Bey.
But, is it wise to seek battle without
learning the truth?
Dündar Bey, if only wisdom was
needed for battle...
... many small ones couldn't
take over big ones.
What our council lacks is courage,
Dündar Bey.
What it lacks is courage.
My father, Dündar Bey...
... has set his heart to Ertuğrul Bey's
cause.
By doing this, when he was just a
child, he proved his bravery.
Now, no one should try to question
my father's bravery.
We tried trading, they attempted an
assassination.
Our Aybars became a martyr.
My brother Osman is struggling
desperately in a bottomless well.
Battling is our job. But...
... patience, is our guide.
Until we hear from Osman, I say we
don't take action.
- I hope nothing's wrong.
- What is going on?
Thank goodness!
Osman Bey is coming!
Thank goodness! Osman Bey is here.
Thank Allah!
Praise be my Bey! Welcome my Bey!
Take it to the barn.
We can neither leave Osman to infidels...
... nor can we take the chance of battle.
My nephew is right.
It's rather early to go into battle.
We need to wait till Osman returns.
Oh, Osman.
Waiting is useless while treachery is
the matter, Dündar Bey.
I'll tell you if it is war or peace.
Be my guest.
I'm telling you, valiant Beys.
It is time to fight the unrest which has
spread from Kulucahisar.
However...
Fighting with swords only will be nothing
then a cat bite to the enemy.
What do you mean, Osman?
We are facing a tough enemy...
who can strangulate us
with their amplified organs...
as we damage them.
It is time to polish off the infidels
beyond the walls.
The Beys who are here, are
to agree on fighting.
However...
the final decision is Dündar Bey's.
Brother, I didn't realize you grew up
that fast.
In this land, there's no time to be
an immature, brother.
The biggest immaturity is to follow
infidels just to do business.
A decision of war for the Turks' own
benefit should be agreed here today.
Otherwise...
You should know that
you'll cut your own throat.
We face the ones who killed their own
governor and set traps for us.
They started this war by killing
my brother Aybars.
We will pray for the battle.
It's the time to be martyrs,
it's not just a war.
That's all I have to say.
Kayı Beys need to rise for war.
It is time to fight!
Osman Bey is right.
The infidels will not behave well.
Eyvallah (Yes) Osman Bey.
It is time to fight.
Now, tell me.
War or peace?
- Beys saying "war" in distance -
If it is a war, then it is a war.
We'd prefer dying to give our Osman, ...
who is entrusted to us by Ertuğrul Bey,
to infidels hands
I see that...
Beys have already decided.
However, this decision...
is beyond me.
We need to be patient till Ertuğrul Bey
returns.
The war decision is Bey's according to
our traditions.
Now...
Excuse me.
I want to talk to my nephews.
Eyvallah (of course)
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
(In the name of Allah)
Ya Allah!
Yes, my daughter.
Thanks to you...
This sword, the entrustment of Hz. Ahmet
Yesevi is in our hands, my daughter.
With your prayers, politeness,
in sha Allah, father.
The best politeness is a person's
effort...
and the best prayer is his actions,
my daughter.
You succeded in a very important job.
Because this sword is not like...
the other dark sword which sinks
into the heart.
This sword shows up in the most difficult
times and...
reach to the new Hakan ( Turkish ruler )
of the Turks.
When the new Hakan of Turks is equipped
with this...
it'll conquer hearts by demolishing the
infidel lands.
This will give hope to the oppressed, and
fear the cruel...
with the spiritual light which
is spread from here.
How will we find that Hakan among all
those people, father?
Is there a way?
We'll find him, my daughter.
We'll find that spark that didn't blow out
despite the whole winter.
Because, when we connect this sword to
that spark...
it will turn into a volcano...
and it will distribute help to the
oppressed.
Who is that Hakan
( Turkish ruler), father?
He is a man who doesn't hesitate to
fight the cruels.
He is also wise, as well as being strong.
And he helps the oppressed.
He is a man, son of a man.
So, the situation is obvious...
I offer that we shall conquer Kulucahisar
castle.
If we succeeded, we'd conquer
all the castles.
Thus we will be freed of Mongol and
Byzantine attack.
We'll plant Islam's flag everywhere.
Easy, nephew.
Easy.
Why are you so fast?
You stayed in that castle knowing that
you'll be accused of the murder, right?
Yes, uncle.
Because the murderer of the Governor is
also my brother Aybar's murderer.
Osman.
You don't hide anything from us,
do you, brother?
What can I hide after all the information,
brother?
Our efforts on you were worth it, Osman.
You qualified your weapon, and you
qualified being the son of a Bey.
I, as your uncle, am proud of you.
Do you really proud of me despite the
fact that they abducted Aygül, uncle?
The enemy is always evil, nephew.
It's not your fault that what happened to
my daughter.
Eyvallah ( thank you ), uncle.
You dived into the castle like
a blunt dagger.
Infidels held you responsible
for every case.
What I am trying to say is, protect
yourself until Ertuğrul Bey returns.
I trust you, Osman.
Watch out for yourself and your Alps(men).
Don't worry, uncle.
As long as the castle keeps calm...
I can look after myself and my Alps.
May Allah help us.
Excuse me, uncle.
I will find out what you are hiding from
me, and what kind of trouble...
you are in, Osman.
At that time, we'll confront again.
We'll confront.
Master Yannis, the light in your face
tells me that the news is important.
Nizameddin, our man in the bazaar.
He writes about the new bazaar.
- Osman is with them also.
- As I predicted.
Osman is with them.
It is obvious the Ahis (The Ahi Brotherhood)
gathered in new bazaar.
- We need to prevent that.
- We will, Kalanoz, we will.
We will crush the bazaar and kill
all of them.
If I attack them with my soldiers, that
declares the war, but I am ready to fight.
It is too early for a war.
Besides, someone else will do it for you.
Who can do this except for me, Master
Yannis?
Prince Salvador, the bloody blade of
Catalonia.
With my fearless warriors,
I am under your command, Master Yannis.
Alaca.
Come on, here.
Here you go.
My uncle praises me.
He talks so sweetly, Alaca.
It doesn't bode well, does it?
It doesn't bode well.
But, my uncle is a wise man.
He is trying to comfort me...
and then act like who he really is.
Masha Allah. ( touch wood! )
Don't worry, you'll be fine soon.
Come on.
Osman Bey.
I was going mad while waiting for
you.
Are you angry with me for what happened?
You have gone through a lot because of me.
I continue living thanks to you.
May Allah be pleased with you.
You are from my blood, Aygül Hatun (lady).
Your life comes first.
Whose horse is this?
Because of the herb he ate.
She is a peddler girl's horse.
I offered my aunt's balm.
I'll take her to the new bazaar and
deliver.
- Be careful, Osman Bey.
- Eyvallah ( Thank you ).
The horse...
eh...
- is a peddler girl's horse.
- a peddler girl?
If a man takes a Hatun's (lady) horse to
her tent...
It means that he loves her.
Alaca, come on.
Come.
Come on, beauty.
Welcome, Gonca Hatun (lady).
Just rest, Bala Hatun.
We've gone through a lot.
You can't imagine how I desperately
want to get back to my job, Gonca Hatun.
Who are they, Bala Hatun (lady)?
A couple of lovers.
Aslı and Kerem.
If they are lovers,
why are they separated?
I heard their story from an Allepon
traveller.
Kerem misses Aslı so much that he
is reduced to his ashes.
And Aslı sweeps the ashes with her
hair.
So, their meeting is due to the judgment
day, and only their story is left for us.
What can I say, Bala? May Allah
give us a love that can be reached.
Amin.
I hope his uncle doesn't get angry when
Osman meets him.
Osman Bey has beaten up the enemy.
Don't worry.
He will get over these, too.
Also...
my Sheik (Bey) has also accepted him.
Would he have accepted him if he hadn't
seen the light in Osman, Gonca Hatun?
Teokles hasn't arrived yet.
Maybe he have been captured by Osman?
Damn it.
If he makes him speak, things will go bad.
It'll be so hard for us to find the treasure.
Commander Andreas!
Yes, madam.
I sent Teoklas after Osman.
He hasn't returned.
Find him, Andreas.
No matter what, find him.
They are hiding what they know from us.
- Can I?
- Come, Samsa.
Long-time no see.
What a surprise to see you, Samsa.
We left you at that castle alone, but...
you were able to manage it.
We are blood brothers, Samsa.
Infidels must have been surprised, too.
Let's sit.
Infidels will panic when Teokles
doesn't show up.
- Who the hell is Teokles?
- The dog they sent to kill me.
Now, we captured him.
I know it, my Osman, I know it.
I know you will take revenge for
my Aybars.
Teokles will lead us to the
murderers of Aybars.
Eyvallah son, Eyvallah ( thank you )
I'll regret them killing a Kayı's valiant.
I, as Erturul Ghazi's son Osman, ...
will skin them to the bones.
- May I?
- Come, Boran Alp.
What happened, Boran?
Why are you looking worried?
Osman Bey...
- Teokles escaped.
- How come?!
I entrusted him to you, didn't I, Boran?
Answer me!
How couldn't you take care of a man whose
ankles and wrists were tied?
Weren't you there?
My Bey, I healed him, then I went to
hunting for him.
He wasn't there when I came back.
The rope was cut by a dagger.
- Someone must have helped.
- Who is that? Who!
Can I, Dündar Bey?
Come, son, come.
- I have something to tell you, father.
- Go on.
Osman.
What did he do?
He captured one of Sofia's hunters,
Teokles.
Where is he?
Don't worry, father. I saved him
from Osman's hands
Could you receive any information?
After Osman escaped
from the castle, she sent him to get him.
Who sent him?
Sofia.
Osman beat up Teokles so bad, but he
is fine now.
Where is that infidel now?
We have him, father.
This information will save Bithynia from a
huge war.
Inform Gündüz Bey.
Off you go.
Jackals go to their nooks,
bears go to their caves.
The place where he is going to is obvious.
The castle.
I'll shoot the jackal in its corner,
I'll choke the bear in the cave!
My Osman, those infidels are playful.
This may be a trap to draw you into
the castle.
We need to turn that castle into a grave
for Teokles, so that...
no one can dare to escape from Osman
Bey from now on.
And when we kill him, it'll be a lesson
to everyone.
Sergeant Samsa, it is time to hunt
the castle.
Those animals know me very well.
They haven't face me recently.
The castle will be a good choice,
in sha'Allah. Long live, my valiant!
You made me happy.
- Speaking in Greek -
In God's holy spirit, the bond
in your eyes disappeared now, Kalanoz.
Do you swear on fighting the Turks in the
way of Holy Margarit Church?
I do.
Do you swear on fighting
everything that...
Turk's consider as holy?
I do.
God bless you.
I was ready to raid the new bazaar with my
soldiers, Master Yannis.
I hope Catalans can manage it.
I don't have any doubts, Kalanoz.
You'll do much more when the time comes.
But as you said, they shouldn't suspect
the castle.
Freeze their tent.
The days that we'll kill all of them...
are close, Kalanoz.
But now, we are going to take care of all
the Ahis, and we will not be involved in.
What's more, we'll take back the holy
entrustment.
If the owner of the wood sword
owns it via Edebali, ...
we'll wake the sleeping up.
-Do you understand me?
-Yes, sir.
Welcome aboard, son.
What you told me warmed my heart, Edebali.
This should be such a state that...
justice should revive with it.
The Islam community should find peace.
The cruel should be afraid.
Our morality should uprise.
A`udhu billahi min ash-shaytan ar-rajim...
( I seek protection in Allah from the accursed shaytan)
Bismillahir rahmanir rahim.
(In the name of Allah, the Most Beneficent, the Most Merciful)
"Indeed, We have given you, [ O Muhammad ],"
"a clear conquest"
"That, Allah...
....may forgive for you what preceded of your sin and what will follow"
"And complete his favor upon you and guide you to a straight path"
"will make sure that
you're on the right way."
"And that Allah
may help thee with powerful help"
"It is he Who sent down tranquilitty into the hearts of the believers,
That they may add faith to their faith"
"Allah belong the armies of
the heavens and the earth"
"And Allah is All-Knowing, All-Wise"
"That He may admit
the men and women...
Who believe, to gardens
beneath which rivers flow,
"To abide therein eternally.."
"And remove from them their misdeeds and ever is that, in the sight of Allah, the highest achievement."
"Sadaqa Allaah al-'Azeem."
(Allah Almighty has spoken the truth.)
My Allah...
You're the one who sees...
knows...
and creates everything.
I don't hide anything from you.
Even the most unknown comes
out if it comes to you.
You're the one who knows about
my biggest dreams...
that are beyond me...
my mad passions...
and my thoughts and dreams
that are beyond this land.
You, who have given
me these dreams, this love...
and this passion,
will give me the power.
Oh My Allah.
I had a dream.
Make it real.
Let me carry my father's flag further.
I was in the land when I opened my eyes.
Let me see beyond the waters.
Everywhere is hazy and thick.
We are surrounded by enemies.
With İlay-ı Kelimetullah
(exalting Islam)...
let me enlighten the dark, my Allah.
Amin.
Uncle...
You're right but...
The sky is hazy, the water is blurry.
After all these problems, how will
we trust these infidels?
What if they do something bad?
Fox is the most crafty but...
the bazaar is full of its
fleece, Gündüz Bey.
I care about Osman.
When he hears that we've given Teokles
to the castle, he'll be very angry.
We don't know what he'll do.
Gündüz Bey.
What should we do?
Just for Osman will be angry, will
we fight Kulucahisar?
Uncle.
My father Ertuğrul Bey will return soon.
He'll want to know who's behind the...
murder of Aybars and Governor.
Osman was seen in the castle
that night, so I say that...
we shouldn't give our only proof to them.
We shouldn't but...
what will we do?
Do you think that only they have
the traitors inside their castle?
If they know that we have Teokles...
isn't it a cause of war for them that
Osman was seen in the castle?
Till my brother returns, the trade
agreement with Kulucahisar will continue.
I can't ruin the...
peace he has created because of Osman.
But...
Osman shouldn't know about it.
Now...
where's that bastard?
I tied him in a nook behind Karanlıkdere.
Even the devil can't find him.
Let's go then.
Son...
Moon son... (Ay)
Aybars son...
Brave son...
When I saw you hungry...
I fed you.
When I saw you undressed, I dressed you.
I had gone long way.
I shed blood, I sacrificed
an animal for you.
With a wish and a pray...
I found a son.
I found you.
I found you, son.
Esselamu Aleykum ve Rahmetullah...
("May the peace and mercy of Allah be with you")
Esselamu Aleykum ve Rahmetullah.
The infidels are not that fast.
I recognized you, Tursun.
Who are you?
Osman Bey sent me.
What's it?
Why did you come to the castle?
I'm looking for someone named Teokles.
Tell me from the beginning.
Osman Bey talked.
He'll come the castle in the end.
But...
I don't know if he has come ever.
Wait...
Don't worry about it. We'll find him...
no matter what.
What are these sounds?
Dündar Bey and Gündüz Bey.
And Teokles.
Now it's clear who got him.
The Great Father.
It's good to see you.
-We're very happy.
-You're welcome!
It's so good to see you, comrade
Nizamettin.
In a short time, we wish to have
conversations with friends.
We're friendly all.
Many friends know about it.
You should know it too.
With pleasure.
Where are they?
There, near the potter stall.
I was assassinated in your
castle, I remained silent.
You charged my nephew with murder,
I stood for it.
Burçin, the bride of Bamsı Bey
who is one of the Beys of our tent...
was pounded up by you. I was silent.
You abducted my daughter...
My Aygül...
I passed over it.
You put this murderer on my
nephew Osman's tail...
I brought to you with my own hands.
Dündar Bey...
We're so unhappy for what happened. ..
but don't forget that...
my husband was murdered.
Your husband was my friend.
The murder of your friend's suspect
is your nephew Osman.
He escaped from our castle,
not to be on trial.
You sent murderers after him...
to kill him.
Dündar Bey...
if Osman is put on trial and prove
that he's not guilty...
there'll be no problem.
I wish you'd obey our justice to...
show your goodwill and...
brought Osman instead of him.
I last saw Osman in this castle.
If he runs away from a castle
that you secure...
I have nothing to do.
Osman...
will be on trial.
But not here.
In a Söğüt court...
where there are Greeks and Kayıs.
I'm a truth-seeking, Dündar Bey.
I accept your proposal.
Then, here you are.
Go to your room, Teokles.
Have some rest.
The door!
-Feed the horses.
-Okay, my Bey.
-You stay here.
Thief! Thief! Help me!
Help me!
Run! My golds!
My Bey...
My Bey... please forgive me.
Please spare my life, my Bey.
Please, my Bey.
Nizamettin Bey!
I'll punish them.
If I see them here again...
they will die.
They deserved it. Long live, Osman Bey.
Do your duty properly, Nizamettin Bey.
Remember your vow that
there'll be no injustice.
If this happens again...
I'll call you to account.
If someone's insolent, his
tongue will be cut.
If someone's a thief, his
hand will be cut.
He deserved it, Osman Bey.
Take these thieves.
Are you looking for your pouch?
Thank you so much. God bless you.
Are you Osman Bey?
Ertuğrul Bey's son.
You're brave like your father.
God grant you to your loved ones....
and grant us to your fair hands.
Thank you so much.
God bless you.
Thank you.
Aslı and Kerem.
I worked hard for it. It's done.
Great job. It looks beautiful.
But the only thing that is
done is not the tile.
You're very brave, son.
May your fair sword be everlasting.
Thanks, Great Father.
Where do you come from?
Where are you going?
We come from Hayy (Allah),
we go to Hu. (Allah)
We go to Allah with our hearts...
and we travel with our feet.
-May your travel be holy, Great Father.
-Thanks.
I've been travelling all my life but I've
never seen anything like this.
It's priceless but...
how much does it cost, daughter?
You're welcome.
Money comes from people but
Allah gives the abundance.
-It's my gift for you, Great Father.
-Thanks, daughter.
I hope you'll always be happy.
When a lover meets lover,
they become happy.
They become happy.
May Allah watch over you two, farewell.
- What is it, Osman Bey?
- Many wolves wear sheep hides.
And many traitors look like dervishes
wearing circlets and sweaters.
I didn't like this man at all.
You should know.
Neither traitors give up betraying,
nor tyrants give up their tyranny.
We should just stay in the right way.
- Gonca Hatun, you take care of the stall.
- Don't worry.
So he is the Osman Bey,
son of Ertuğrul Gazi.
- He is going to be trouble in the raid.
- Kill Osman in the raid.
But I want Bala,
Edebali's daughter alive.
- We will get what we want from her.
- How did you find out it was Bala Hatun?
I saw her when I came to their
door to be a follower of Ahî Evran.
She was with her father,
she was little back then.
But her eyes, they look the same.
- It came here like the wind.
- How did you cure my Alaca, Osman Bey?
- What was its remedy?
- Its remedy is a little bit balm.
And its love for you, Bala Hatun.
It was so impatient to go to
many adventures with you.
You see, Osman Bey? I am just a
poor artisan on the way of Ahî.
When I saw you weeping near the horse...
- ... I made a promise to myself.
- What promise was that?
I said whoever upsets this Hatun(Lady)...
... is my sworn enemy.
Only the ones we love can upset us,
not our enemies, Osman Bey.
Don't you worry about it.
Osman Bey!
What do you want, bully?
Alişar Bey sent word everywhere,
my Bey. He is looking for you.
He said he wants to welcome you
in his mansion, not as a banner lord...
... but as a hunting friend.
Thank you, we can go there together.
Farewell, Bala Hatun. I will come
to see you as soon as possible.
Osman Bey sends his regards.
Stop!
As Byzantine is full of bastards,
Kayı is full of brave men.
Osman Bey.
Welcome.
- Thank you, Alişar Bey.
- Come in.
Let me serve you basil sherbet, Osman Bey.
I've heard you ruined Kulucahisar Castle.
We are breathing down their necks.
They will see us even in their shadows.
We will surely won't let their slanders,
treacheries go without punishment.
I know you didn't kill the governor.
Because if you had killed him,
not a soul could've known about it.
You would've got out of
that damned castle easily.
If I had doubted you for a second...
As a banner lord, I would've
found you before your uncle...
... thrown you to a dungeon,
had you stand on trial before kadi.
I will drown them with
their own treachery, Alişar Bey.
I will find both of the governor's and
my brother's killers and punish them.
I also want a trial for this.
I want to come to the trial
by myself and be judged.
When we...
... first left this table...
... we were very hopeful.
I assure you Princess Sofia.
My friend Yorgopolos' death,
hurt us the most after you.
When my husband's killer is punished...
... we will renew that
friendship, Dündar Bey.
A permanent peace in these lands
was our biggest dream with Yorgopolos.
Moreover, the most important
legacy that he left is this.
Ma'am.
Theokoles has been killed.
How?
Osman!
He did this!
Osman isn't even here,
Princess, how could that happen?
Only Osman could have done this!
Enough!
The traitors killed your governor too.
We were starting to believe you.
We will discuss this in
the trial, Dündar Bey.
If my nephew is found innocent in the trial
and you still continue to fight him...
... then have it your way.
War, or peace, so be it.
You better know it like this.
So you think the killer of Bamsı Bey's
son and the governor is the same person.
You sneaked into the castle to talk
with the governor for this reason, right?
Right, I also spoke with
governor before he died.
You did? Then tell me everything you know.
The governor told me that the treachery
was spreading from his castle, Alişar Bey.
I was the only one he trusted, neither
his wife nor his Commander Kolonoz.
The war is close, Osman Bey,
and this is no time to be silent.
The war between Kayı and Kulucahisar...
... became a war between
the Seljuk and Byzantine.
Princess Sofia and Commander Kolonoz
wanted you to be put on a trial.
You escaped from the dungeon too.
The trial should be on our lands.
- Why? What are you afraid of?
- Princess Sofia...
... Commander Kolonoz...
... they wanted to kill me
before I was on trial.
- You must have strong evidence for that.
- You can be sure about that, Alişar Bey.
When the trial begins, everyone will see.
I will prove both of them are the killers.
What are you talking about Osman Bey,
do you have any idea what...
-... will that lead to?
- As long as you stand with the truth...
... they should be afraid, not me.
I say, if they are the target of a
hunter like you, they are doomed.
If we draw them to our hunting grounds...
... I will make them sing
like nightingales.
You just need to trust me, Alişar Bey.
You have my word, Osman
Bey, I will do what it takes.
Did you see that man?
I crushed his head with my axe!
We smashed them up!
Brave sons of Catalonia!
Lion-hearted warriors of Prince Salvador!
Are you ready to leave
terrible nightmares after you?
- Are you ready?
- Yes!
They will call us "ruthless
warriors of Prince Salvador"!
They will scare their
children with our stories.
Pregnant women will miscarry
when they hear our names!
Young boys' hairs will
turn grey from the fear!
For Prince Salvador! For the
treasures waiting for us!
- Now is the time for battle!
- Salvador!
Salvador!
Are you sure, Sergeant Samsa?
Like my faith, Osman Bey.
My uncle, my brother!
Batur!
I saw it myself.
That infidel called Theokoles was
between Dündar Bey and Gündüz Bey.
Batur was behind them.
So they handed the man who
Princess Sofia hired to kill me...
... the biggest leverage I had to find my
brother Aybars' killers to the castle?
Both my uncle and my
brother was in the tent.
So...
... Batur is the one who went
after Bora and kidnapped Theokoles.
Batur, huh?
Batur, Batur!
He will pay for this treachery!
What are you going to do, Osman Bey?
I will put them on the most righteous
trial, Konur Alp! I will make the trial!
My witnesses will be my martyr brother
Aybars, and Yorgopolos who was killed.
The kadi of my trial will be my anger,
the executioner will be my sword!
I will judge them myself!
They didn't say "There's good in
every bad." for nothing, Gündüz.
You are right uncle, Theokoles' death
also proved my brother Osman's innocence.
You are just in time,
daughter, I was so thirsty.
- Enjoy your drink, father.
- Thank you.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim. (In the name of
Allah, the Most Beneficent, the Most Merciful.)
Thank you.
Now that their game is exposed,
they can no longer blame Osman.
Uncle.
We want to do business,
trades with these men but...
... I say this castle is
boiling like a cauldron.
First, the assassination of the governor,
now that man called Theokoles.
It seems there is a big conflict
behind those stone walls.
That's better, my nephew,
the more that place boils...
... the more we benefit from it.
You are talking nicely,
that's good, but...
... what if Osman is not
as innocent as we think?
- What about Dündar Bey and Batur, my Bey?
- They will all pay for this!
Sergeant Samsa, you can stop now.
Don't worry, we are with Osman Bey.
- You look so happy Bala Hatun.
- My Alaca is here.
How is Alaca now?
It seems Osman Bey healed your
horse, since you are so happy.
I don't know if his hands are blessed,
he healed my horse in one night.
but...
... he is surely feeling something if
he brought it back in one night.
What are you trying to tell, Gonca Hatun?
Don't hold yourself.
I asked the customers coming from Kayı,
Osman Bey doesn't have a wife.
A brave man like him always has a lover.
I asked about it thoroughly,
he doesn't have a lover either.
And why are you telling
me all this, Gonca Hatun?
I saw how he looked at you at the stall.
Aslı and Kerem, you did a
great job, it's beautiful, but...
... It's not just the porcelain,
your horse's treatment is also done.
He jumped into the danger for Aygül
Hatun without a second thought.
She's his uncle's daughter,
what would've he done?
He wouldn't let her die, would he?
And, would that be an action worthy
of a famous man like Osman?
Are you jealous?
Put these jugs on the stalls.
- And take a look at the empty stalls.
- Don't be stubborn, Bala Hatun.
I can take a look at the stalls,
but you should take a look at your heart.
- Good day to you, sisters.
- Good day to you too.
- Welcome.
- Thank you, lady.
There's a white horse in the
stable, they said it was yours.
- What happened to my Alaca?
- He was restless all of a sudden...
... now he is dying. You should
come and take a look, sister.
- I'm going there Gonca.
- Okay, Bala Hatun.
- Can you watch over the stall?
- Don't worry, sister.
I'm here sister!
You are so beautiful.
It's such a pity.
Take her!
Attack the market,
kill everyone! Go!
Welcome, Osman Bey!
You won't be able to
get away with this, Osman.
There's no excuse for foulness...
... and no relief from treachery.
What are you doing, my Bey?
You are still a foul one, my uncle's son.
Now!
Listen to me carefully!
Whoever causes unrest, become a traitor...
... whoever tries to play foul
games behind my back...
... I...
Osman, son of Ertuğrul Gazi...
... swear on the holy
hide my father sat on...
... and on the banner
which we live under...
... and...
... on my black sword
that I carry on my belt...
... I won't have mercy!
I will swallow like a flood,
I will burn like fire!
I will cut the ears that
don't listen to my warnings...
... and the tongues that say
anything else on my words!
Let it be known, and be said like this!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com